const collectionsData = [
  {
    _id: 1,
    title: 'Ordering Food in Spanish',
    creator: 'Jeff Who', 
    createdAt: 'today', 
    flashcards: [
      {
        front: 'Buenos Días',
        back: 'Good Morning',
        importance: 'normal'
      },
      {
        front: 'Me gustaría una tortilla por favor',
        back: 'I would like an omelette please',
        importance: 'high'
      },
      {
        front: 'Dónde está el restaurante?',
        back: 'Where is the restaurant',
        importance: 'normal'
      },
      {
        front: 'La comida es muy cara',
        back: 'The food is very expensive',
        importance: 'normal'
      },

    ]
  },
  {
    _id: 2,
    title: 'Introduce yourself in Spanish',
    creator: 'Fabian04HV', 
    createdAt: '1 year ago', 
    flashcards: [
      {
        front: 'Hola, me llamo Felipe Hernandez',
        back: 'Hello, my name is Felipe Hernandez',
        importance: 'normal'
      },
      {
        front: 'Cómo te llamas?',
        back: 'What is your name?',
        importance: 'normal'
      },
      {
        front: 'Tengo 19 años',
        back: 'I am 19 years old',
        importance: 'normal'
      },
      {
        front: 'Cuántos años tienes?',
        back: 'How old are you?',
        importance: 'normal'
      },
      {
        front: 'De dónde eres?',
        back: 'Where are you from?',
        importance: 'normal'
      },
      {
        front: 'Soy de Berlin',
        back: 'I am from Berlin',
        importance: 'normal'
      },

    ]
  }

]

export default collectionsData